(Amy:)Wil, that was a little wooden.
- Wooden?
- Don't worry, it wasn't terrible.
(Amy:)Just this time,
try to say it the way people sound.
(Amy:)And action.
(Sheldon:)My friend Wil Wheaton.
Hi, thanks for having me.
I'm excited to be here.
- So, Wil, what do you have for us first?
- Well, this is an exciting one.
(Wil:)This is the flag
of the United Federation of Planets.
(Wil:)- Now, what's interesting about this flag...
- Cut.
- What was wrong with that?
- It's called Fun With Flags.
(Amy:)They're not at half-mast. Nobody died.
Let's try and keep it upbeat.
Um, no offense,
but I've been acting since I was a kid.
(Wil:)I can handle a web show
without a lot of direction.
(Sheldon:)It's true.
(Sheldon:)In 1982 Wil played the voice
of Martin the mouse in The Secret of NIMH.
(Sheldon:)You moved me.
(Amy:)You'll have to forgive me.
(Amy:)This is my first time directing.
I just want it to be good.
- So do I.
- Great.